The “American Dream” promises that in the Land of Opportunity, any individual can climb the economic ladder and prosper through hard work and ambition alone.
“美国梦”承诺，在这片机遇之地，任何人仅凭努力和抱负，就能沿着经济阶梯向上攀登，走向富足。
And yet, young Americans today are struggling to earn more than their parents did at the same age, and upward mobility in the US actually compares unfavourably to that of other industrialised nations.
然而，如今的美国年轻人很难挣得比父母同龄时更多，而且美国的向上流动性实际上还比不上其他工业化国家。
So why does the idea of the American Dream persist?
那么，“美国梦”这一观念为何依然存在？
A new study in the American Journal of Political Science identifies one factor that has been overlooked: the influence of reality TV.
《美国政治学杂志》上的一项新研究找出了一个一直被忽视的因素：真人秀节目的影响。
Reality shows have come to dominate US television over the past 20 years, notes Eunji Kim from Vanderbilt University.
范德比尔特大学的金恩智指出，过去20年间，真人秀节目已逐渐在美国电视界占据主导地位。
And the overwhelming majority of these have a “rags-to-riches” storyline: they feature ordinary Americans who work hard to achieve great economic success.
而且，其中绝大多数节目都有“白手起家”的故事情节：节目的主角是靠努力奋斗取得巨大经济成功的普通美国人。
And while these programmes are regularly among the most-watched shows, news broadcasts—which paint a more realistic view of the economic hardship faced by millions of Americans—get a much smaller proportion of the viewership.
此外，这些节目常常跻身收视率最高的节目之列，而新闻节目虽然更真实地描绘了数百万美国人所面临的经济困境，所占的收视份额却要小得多。
Rags-to-riches stories are ubiquitous on TV—but does watching these programmes actually convince people that economic mobility is easily attainable?
白手起家的故事在电视上无处不在，但观看这些节目真的会让人们相信，经济地位的提升很容易实现吗？
To find out, Kim’s team had participants watch a 5-minute clip from a reality show with a rags-to-riches storyline.
为了弄清楚这一点，金恩智的团队让参与者观看了一段5分钟的真人秀片段，该节目的故事情节围绕白手起家展开。
Control participants watched a clip from a reality show that didn’t have a rags-to-riches story.
对照组参与者观看的则是一段不含白手起家故事的真人秀片段。
After watching the shows, participants rated how much they agreed with four statements relating to the American Dream.
看完节目后，参与者就四条与“美国梦”有关的陈述，给自己的认同程度打分。
The results showed that those who’d watched a rags-to-riches clip did indeed have a significantly greater belief in the American Dream.
结果显示，看过白手起家片段的人对“美国梦”的信念确实显著更强。
Interestingly, when participants were separated by party affiliation, this effect was significant among Republicans but not Democrats, suggesting that the kind of messages implicit in these TV shows may play into people’s existing socioeconomic beliefs.
有趣的是，按党派归属将参与者分组后，这一效应在共和党人中显著，在民主党人中则不显著；这表明，这些电视节目中隐含的那类信息可能会契合并强化人们已有的社会经济观念。
Kim also conducted a survey of 3,000 US residents.
金恩智还对3000名美国居民开展了一项调查。
They also rated the extent to which they believed success in life is related to various internal factors (such as ambition) and external factors (such as family wealth).
这些受访者还评定了自己在多大程度上认为，人生成功与各种内在因素（如抱负）和外在因素（如家庭财富）有关。
Finally, they read a list of TV programmes and indicated which they regularly watched.
最后，他们看了一份电视节目清单，并指出自己经常收看其中哪些节目。
Participants who were heavy or frequent viewers of rags-to-riches programmes had a stronger belief in the American Dream than those who never watched such shows.
与从不收看这类节目的人相比，大量或频繁收看白手起家类节目的参与者对“美国梦”的信念更强。
Kim concludes that “rags-to-riches entertainment media are an important cultural force that promotes and perpetuates beliefs in upward mobility”.
金恩智的结论是，“白手起家类娱乐媒体是一股重要的文化力量，宣扬并延续着对向上流动的信念”。
And here’s the problem: if people mistakenly believe that hard work is all that is needed for individuals to make a better life for themselves, they may be less supportive of policies that could actually combat inequality.
而问题就在于：如果人们误以为个人只需努力就能为自己创造更好的生活，他们可能就不那么支持那些真正能够遏制不平等的政策。
“In this era of choice, entertainment media are what captures hearts and minds,” Kim writes.
金恩智写道：“在这个选择众多的时代，俘获人心的正是娱乐媒体。”
“Its political consequences are anything but trivial.”
“其政治后果绝非无足轻重。”